joyofkosher.com 2017-11-19

# Privacy Policy - Joy of Kosher

**Last Updated: June 8, 2016**

Welcome to _JOY of KOSHER with Jamie Geller_ , the #1 kosher food and cooking community website located at _[www.JOYofKOSHER.com](http://www.joyofkosher.com/)_ (the "Website") operated by Kosher Media Holdings LLC, a New York limited liability company with an address at 1575 50th Street, 4th Floor, Brooklyn, NY 11219 (“KMH”, "we", "our", or "us"). This privacy policy (this “Privacy Policy”) is intended to inform you about how KMH collects, uses and stores your personally identifiable information (“PII”) and other information in operating the Website.

 **How does the Website Work?**

The Website enables visitors to the Website (“Users”, “you”, or “your”) to learn more about us and to navigate the Website. Your use of the Website is subject to KMH’s Terms of Use agreement, which can be found at _[www.joyofkosher.com/terms-of-use](http://www.joyofkosher.com/page/terms-of-use/)_.

You can make general use of the Website without providing any PII to KMH. However, you may need to provide us or third parties with certain of your PII in order to use certain of the Website’s functionality, such as making purchases of our products and/or services or posting comments through your social media account or other third party services (each, if available). 

By using the Website, you consent to the collection and use of your PII and other information by KMH as described in this Privacy Policy.

 **How can the terms of this Privacy Policy be modified?**

We reserve the right to change how we handle and use the information that we collect through the Website, and to modify this Privacy Policy, at any time in our sole discretion. You agree to review this Privacy Policy periodically to be aware of all such modifications. You further agree that your continued use of the Website after a modified version of this Privacy Policy has been posted shall be deemed to be your conclusive acceptance of any modified version of this Privacy Policy. We will indicate that changes to this Privacy Policy have been made by updating the date indicated after “Last Updated” at the beginning of this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to abide by the initial version and each modified version of this Privacy Policy, as applicable, then you are not authorized to use the Website. A current version of this Privacy Policy is accessible via the footer of the Website’s homepage.

 **What type of PII does KMH collect from you and how do we use it?**

You need to provide us with certain PII in order to purchase our products and/or services through the Website or in connection with the Website, including without limitation your name and email address, and payment information. You may also need to provide us with certain PII in order to use other Website functionality. 

KMH may provide your PII to individuals or entities who work on our behalf or with us. These individuals or entities may use your PII to help fulfill your requests and to help us communicate with you about different products, services or resources offered through the Website. For example, we will share your PII with our e-commerce service provider and/or shipping companies in order to fulfill purchases made by you. We also may transfer or permit the transfer of certain of your PII or other information to other service providers and other third parties who assist us in operating the Website. 

**How else do we use your PII?**

KMH may also use and disclose PII to improve and enhance your experience on the Website and for other purposes. For example, from time to time, we may use and share PII with third parties to show general demographic and preference information among Website users. In these circumstances, however, the shared information will neither contain nor be linked to any of your PII.

Further, KMH may share your PII with third parties for direct marketing and other purposes, and in such a case you acknowledge that the handling of your PII by such third parties will not be governed by the terms of this Privacy Policy, but rather by the terms of whatever privacy policy or other privacy protocols such third party may provide, if any. If you would rather us not share your PII with any third party for direct marketing or other purposes, please either (1) do not submit PII to KMH, or (2) indicate your desire for us not to share your PII with third parties for direct marketing purposes by submitting such a request in writing (an “Opt-Out Request”) to us at: Kosher Media Holdings LLC, 1575 50th Street, 4th Floor, Brooklyn, NY 11219, or by email at _[optout@thejoyofkosher.com](mailto:optout@joyofkosher.com)_. 

Please note that it may take several weeks for us to comply with each Opt-Out Request, and until we are able to comply with such request we may continue to use your PII as described in this Privacy Policy. Please note that after receiving your Opt-Out Request, we may continue to maintain your name and other PII to help us ensure that we can honor such a request, to communicate to you about any transactions made by you (if applicable), and for other purposes not related to direct marketing.

Please note that if we receive your Opt-Out Request after having shared your PII with a third party or parties for direct marketing purposes or having otherwise transferred or disposed of your PII, we may not have the ability to control the use of such PII by any third party, and in such an event you agree that KMH shall not be responsible or liable, directly or indirectly, for any damages or loss caused or alleged to be caused by or caused by or otherwise related to the use of such PII by any such third party or resulting from any such transfer or disposition. If you are concerned about us sharing your PII with third parties or otherwise transferring or disposing of your PII, you should not provide your PII to us.

 **Under what other circumstances may we release PII?**

In addition to sharing your PII with third parties as described above, we may also release your PII to other third parties if we believe that such release is necessary (a) to comply with the law (e.g., a legal process or a statutory authorization or requirement) or a court order, (b) in order to apply or enforce the Terms of Use, (c) to protect you, other Website users, or us from fraudulent, abusive, or unlawful use of the Website, or (d) if we reasonably believe that a danger to any person or property requires the disclosure of such PII or otherwise if we believe such a disclosure is needed to protect our interests (as determined by us in our sole discretion).

Our rights under this Privacy Policy may be automatically assigned by KMH, in our sole discretion, to a third party or parties, and such an assignment will inure to the benefit of our successors, assigns and/or licensees. Without limitation of the foregoing, we may sell, transfer or otherwise share some or all of our assets, including without limitation your PII, with any parent company, subsidiary, joint venture, and/or any company under our common control, as well as to a potential acquirer and/or an acquirer, including without limitation in connection with a merger, reorganization, or sale of assets or stock, or in the event of bankruptcy. In each such instance, the PII we have collected from you may be one of the assets transferred in connection with such a transaction.

 **What other information does KMH collect?**

We may also collect anonymous and aggregate information from you about your preferences in navigating the Website by using cookies, action tags and other methods. Cookies are small text files that identify your computer. We may use cookies to, among other things, monitor usage of the Website, customize features of the Website, identify your computer operating system and browser, and complete transactions. An action tag is a small, graphic image on a webpage that is designed to allow the website owner or a third party to monitor who is visiting a website by collecting the IP address of the computer to which the tag is sent, the URL of the webpage that the tag comes from and the time at which such webpage was viewed. Action tags may be associated with cookie information. We may also use such anonymous and aggregate information for promotional and other business purposes.

Furthermore, the Website includes the ability for you to interact with the Website using certain social media features, such as logging in from your Facebook or Twitter accounts. These features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on the Website, and may set a cookie, tag or other device such as a widget to enable such a feature to function properly. Such social media features and devices are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on the Website. Your interactions with these features are governed either by this Privacy Policy or by the privacy policy of the company providing such features, as applicable.

 **Do I have the ability not to be identified by KMH?**

Yes. If you do not want to be identified by us, you can set your browser to warn you before accepting cookies and refuse cookies when your browser alerts you to their presence. You can also adjust the settings in your browser to refuse all cookies. If you do not want us to have any of your PII, do not submit any of your PII to us. Please keep in mind that if you refuse cookies you may not be able to use certain of the Website’s functionality.

 **How do we store information?**

KMH takes steps consistent with commercially reasonable industry standards to secure PII collected from you from loss, misuse, unauthorized access and destruction while under our control. However, please note that despite our efforts to protect information provided to us, we cannot guarantee that such information (including your PII) will not be lost, disclosed or accessed by accidental circumstances or by the unauthorized acts of others.

 **Does KMH provide links to other websites?**

KMH may provide links to other websites or resources of possible interest to you. The collection and use of your PII and other information by such websites shall be subject to the policies and procedures of such websites and not those contained in this Privacy Policy. For instance, the information collected by our service providers, including without limitation our e-commerce provider, in executing transactions you have requested through the Website, is subject to the privacy policies of such third parties and is not subject to this Privacy Policy.

 **What are our policies regarding children?**

The Website is intended for general use by persons who have reached the age of consent in their state of residence and it is not targeted to anyone under thirteen (13) years of age. KMH does not knowingly collect PII from anyone under thirteen (13) years of age. If we learn that we have unwittingly collected PII from anyone under thirteen (13) years of age, we will promptly delete such information.

 **Do we have a mechanism to address the removal of PII and complaints about the handling of information that we collect?**

If you wish to remove PII that you have submitted to KMH, please send us an email requesting such removal to _[info@joyofkosher.com](mailto:info@joyofkosher.com)_. If you have questions or concerns about any of our information collection or handling practices, please contact us at _info@joyofkosher.com_ or write to us at Kosher Media Holdings LLC, 1575 50th Street, Suite 400, Brooklyn, NY 11219.
